<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- generator="REDIF2XML https://github.com/danvoinea/redif2xml" -->
<records><record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>3</startPage><endPage>12</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">Globalisation, Tradition And Cultural Identity In Spanish Football: Reflections And Observations</title><authors><author><name>Jim O'Brien</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">Southampton Solent University, United Kingdom</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">This article offers some reflections and observations on the complex relationship between the forces of Globalisation and Spanish football, posing the key question as to whether the impact of Globalisation has been a quintessentially corrosive dynamic, eroding the quasi - sacrosanct traditions of the Spanish game to fashion a distinctive post- modern pastiche of elitism and inequality based on an orgy of consumption and commodity.</abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-3-12.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>football</keyword><keyword> identity</keyword><keyword> mass populism</keyword><keyword> world cup</keyword><keyword> iconography</keyword></keywords></record>
<record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>13</startPage><endPage>23</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">University Students Grit Level And Grit Achievement Relation </title><authors><author><name>Omer Beyhan</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">NEU, A.K. Education Faculty, Curriculum Development &amp; Teaching Branch Meram/Konya/Turkey</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">Grit is explaining in Dictionary of the Turkish language Association as determination and desire to have identified the level of long-term goals. Duckworth, Peterson, Matthews, and Kelly (2007) are definiting it as, perseverance and passion for Long-Term Goals. In addition to stating that grit is an important factor in measuring the intelligence and the success. At the same time they have stressed that the grit is much more important predictors of success. Even Duckworth and Quinn (2009) argued that grit is more effective than intelligence scores for explainig the success. There are some studies that they are advocating grit is closely associated with self-discipline, self-regulation and goal orientation, and grit is the main factor for exlaining that concpts(Duckworth &amp; Quinn, 2009; Peterson &amp; Seligman, 2004). In this study, university student success and their grit's are analysed. Therefore, determining the relationship between success and grit is used for descriptive screening model. This study was conducted with 451 students in Education Faculty at Necmettin Erbakan University in 2015-2016 academic year spring semester. In order to data collecting "Grit-S scale",  developed by Duckworth and Quinn (2009) and adapted to Turkish by Sarıcam and others (2015), was used. Datum were analysed by SPSS 16 soft ware and frequency, mean, standard deviation and regresion test were used as statistical techniques. The achievement scores of students have found a significant correlation between the grit scores.</abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-13-23.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>Grit</keyword><keyword> Achievement</keyword><keyword> descriptive model</keyword><keyword> Correlation</keyword><keyword> Regression</keyword></keywords></record>
<record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>24</startPage><endPage>35</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">Perspectives And Modalities In Order To Develop The Didactic Staff's Intercultural Competences</title><authors><author><name>Claudiu Marian Bunaiasu</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author><author><name>Alexandru Constantin Strunga</name><email></email><affiliationId>2</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName><affiliationName affiliationId="2">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">The purpose of the study is to analyse the impact of some perspectives, strategies, and programs, in order to develop the intercultural dimension of the professional competence profile, regarding the teaching career. The investigation tools are represented by the questionnaire and the focus group, applied to a sample of 110 subjects. The results of the research emphasize: a) the social and educational necessity in order to train the didactic staff's intercultural competence; b) the subjects 'options for programs of intercultural psychology, intercultural communication, the didactic methodology of the intercultural education; c) the subjects' adhesion to creating a European curricular framework, in order to acclimatize the teachers to an intercultural environment. The results achieved emphasize the idea of adopting the transformational curricular model as part of the intercultural curricula, in order to train the teachers and to synchronize specific strategies as part of European countries.</abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-24-35.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>intercultural education</keyword><keyword> cultural diversity</keyword><keyword> European conscience</keyword><keyword> didactic staff's intercultural competences</keyword><keyword> intercultural curriculum</keyword></keywords></record>
<record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>36</startPage><endPage>47</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">Overcoming The Children's Mourning State Through Psychological Intervention</title><authors><author><name>Oprea-Valentin Busu</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author><author><name>Antonia Ioana Luchici</name><email></email><affiliationId>2</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName><affiliationName affiliationId="2">University of Bucharest, Romania</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">Death and mourning that follows it are experiences that occurs in everyone`s life at one time. There are unavoidable, painful, sad experiences even for adults who are able to manage their own emotions, and evenmore for children who, at least in early childhood and elementary school aren't able to understand on their own what it's happening in that moment, and how to manage their sadness and live the mourning period properly. Due to the fact that children are not yet fully developed cognitively, cannot understand on their own the concept of death. At that age, death seems for them not to be permanent. Children believe that death is a reversible process that the person in their family is temporarily left and they will return at any moment, and they will wait and ask for that moment long after the actual death, if lacked of any other information. Moreover, children think that death is avoidable, since - at that age, self-centeredness is somehow a characteristic of their personality and death hasn't affected their own person; therefore, when death occurs in their family, their reality will be brutally shaken and they will be very disoriented. Also, in early childhood, kids have a symbolic, magical perspective about death; they imagine it as a devil, a monster or a black lady with a scythe and many other images, far from a realistic perspective. Considering this aspects, it is very important that a realistic, honest, adapted to their age perspective of death when it affects their family. Unfortunately, in many cultures, death is still a taboo. It still exists the belief of overprotecting children from suffering by hiding the death of a close family member, lying them and taking them far away so that they cannot see the dead person. But actually, by practicing this, parents, teachers and persons around the children only make him be more disoriented and suffer more by not knowing what happened with the person they love. As a parent or teacher, it is very important to understand that staying beside the children and sustaining him emotionally, without hiding him any aspect about death of the loved one has a crucial importance for their future development; otherwise, it is probable that they will develop symptoms of chronic depression, and as adults, problems of attachment and extreme fear of death. Proper education for population regarding this delicate subject is a sign of a developed society. In the light of this perspectives, specialists and psychotherapists should be prepared to offer advice and support in any moment so that parents will be learn how to stand by their children in the hard and long process of managing their negative emotions, living their mourning together.</abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-36-47.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>death</keyword><keyword> mourning</keyword><keyword> sadness</keyword><keyword> emotional management</keyword><keyword> psychotherapy</keyword><keyword> psychological intervention</keyword></keywords></record>
<record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>48</startPage><endPage>54</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">The Dimension Of The Socio-Cultural Brand Of Coca-Cola</title><authors><author><name>Florentina Manuela Dumitrescu</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">Today, advertising is undoubtedly one of the most fascinating social phenomena, a fundamental factor influencing individuals, attitudes or lifestyles. It is an important element of contemporary culture, deeply anchored in our cultural heritage. In this framework encompasses our article, aiming to demonstrate influential aspects of the Coca-Cola advertising slogan as an instrument of culture and ideology, in a few words, a merciless mirror of our society.</abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-48-54.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>advertising</keyword><keyword> slogans</keyword><keyword> culture</keyword><keyword> language</keyword><keyword> communication</keyword></keywords></record>
<record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>55</startPage><endPage>70</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">The General Framework Of Accounting Within The Projects Financed From Structural Funds</title><authors><author><name>Alina-Georgiana Motoi</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author><author><name>Aurelia Dumitru</name><email></email><affiliationId>2</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName><affiliationName affiliationId="2">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">In this article are analysed the main aspects which lead to creating an optimal accounting framework. Talking about the elements, of accounting legal framework, we refer to accounting general principles and in particular, to the principles applied in the domain of structural funds. The article aims to gather all the directives, laws and regulations which stipulate the principles and the major changes, appeared, all over the periods of time . Also, it is highlighted the grade and the way in which every accounting principle is implemented in the area of structural funds. The researching methodology is based on qualitative method, and is completed by the quantitative one, putting the accent on the theoretical and practical aspects of the problems mentioned above, from a descriptive conceptual perspective. </abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-55-70.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>structural funds</keyword><keyword> principles</keyword><keyword> accounting</keyword><keyword> directives</keyword><keyword> regulations</keyword></keywords></record>
<record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>71</startPage><endPage>79</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">A Possible Barrier In Extending The Process Of Lifelong Learning (Lll)</title><authors><author><name>Emil Lazar</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">The process of accumulating cognitive and socio-emotional proficiencies is accomplished mainly during the first period of a person's life. These proficiencies assure a basis for the ulterior accumulation of specific skills through vocational and technical education, superior education and lifelong learning. Employees have limited access to information about their training opportunities, and employers do not benefit of stimuli so that they might offer a professional formation. A comparative approach regarding necessary skills categories on labor market may be very useful from the education and formation point of view.</abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-71-79.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>proficiencies</keyword><keyword> obstacles</keyword><keyword> expansion</keyword><keyword> LLL</keyword></keywords></record>
<record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>80</startPage><endPage>88</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">Penal Policies In Bulgaria And Poland</title><authors><author><name>Simona Mihaiu</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">Institute of Sociology, Romanian Academy</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">The contemporary european studies underline the necessity of adoption of an european model, in order to assure the compliance with the fundamental rights and liberties of people deprived of liberty. But the visions of the model favour one of the two opposite tendencies, which are invariable present in theoretical debates and penal politics: on one hand, the use of  the deprive of liberty as a mean to avoid the repetition of an offense and on the other hand, the compliance with the fundamental rights of people deprived of liberty. The article proposes the analysis from a theoretical perspective the European penal politics' impact on the penal politics from Bulgaria and Poland, member states of the European Union. Within this context, it is important to mention the fact that the selection of the two states is underlay on the hypothesis according to which the theoretical and empirical knowledge of the European penal politics' impact on the national penal politics is not developed from the sociological perspective.</abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-80-88.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>European model</keyword><keyword> criminal politics</keyword><keyword> prisoners' rights.</keyword></keywords></record>
<record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>89</startPage><endPage>102</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">Local And European Identity In The Regional Press</title><authors><author><name>Xenia Negrea</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">The study assesses the way the mission of Europeanization is assumed by the press. From this perspective, it is shown that the media has an educational role, even one of emancipation, transgressing the absolute expectation of informing. The study proposes a re-interpretation of the social involvement of journalism, recognizing a pertinent role in setting up the civic and mentality values at local and regional levels. The speech of the online written press was monitored with precise reference to the most important publications in two regions: Oltenia (Romania) and Valencia (Spain).  We understood the journalistic texts as interpretation actions that generate meaning for a community. The thematic fields circumscribing the key terminology were analyzed, texts were evaluated in terms of perspective and of socio-emotional proximity graphics and we have demonstrated the need of subsuming of so-called 'European journalism' with the more complex 'social journalism'.</abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-89-102.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>journalistic roles; proximity; social journalism; European Union; identity. </keyword></keywords></record>
<record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>103</startPage><endPage>112</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">The Role Of The Integrated, Thematic Project To Learning Progress Of The Child In The Early Period</title><authors><author><name>Aida Cornelia Stoian</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">In this study, we have proposed to present you the results of an empirical research in order to identify the positive aspects of the integrated, thematic project in learning progress of children in preschool. Using the observation method, we analyzed children's results regarding the objectives in the respect to the objectives in the grid. Children's progress in learning represents the confirmation and affirmation of the role of this integrated, thematic project in supporting the early learning child.</abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-103-112.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>integrated project</keyword><keyword> learning progress of the child</keyword><keyword> alternative methods</keyword><keyword> interdisciplinarity</keyword><keyword> constructivist strategies</keyword></keywords></record>
<record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>113</startPage><endPage>119</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">New Perspectives Over The Use Of Smartbands In University-Based Health Education Programs</title><authors><author><name>Alexandru Constantin Strunga</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author><author><name>Claudiu Marian Bunaiasu</name><email></email><affiliationId>2</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName><affiliationName affiliationId="2">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">The aim of our case study is to analyze the perceived impact of smartbands on adopting an active and healthy lifestyle by students at the level of university education. Integrating recent contributions from education sciences, knowledge management and applied health informatics, the paper highlights the premises of an institutional educational program that aims to improve students' health (with a special focus on weight loss). Starting from the arguments for using smarbands in health education programs and the current research being made in this field, the authors propose several directions of study and solutions that could be integrated at university level in order to improve students' health. </abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-113-119.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>Smartbands</keyword><keyword> smartphone</keyword><keyword> health education programs</keyword><keyword> case study</keyword><keyword> weight loss</keyword></keywords></record>
<record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>120</startPage><endPage>125</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">Perspectives On Marketing And Organizational Advertising</title><authors><author><name>Alina Tenescu</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">The main objective of this paper is to show several perspectives on marketing and organizational advertising, as fields of research, training and practice. We also aim to highlight the relationship between the two concepts: "marketing" and "advertising of organizations".</abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-120-125.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>organizational advertising</keyword><keyword> organizational marketing</keyword><keyword> perspectives</keyword><keyword> practice</keyword><keyword> research</keyword><keyword> training</keyword></keywords></record>
<record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>126</startPage><endPage>130</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">An Extended Review For A Remarkable Book: Systemic Approaches To Strategic Management </title><authors><author><name>Bianca Teodorescu</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author><author><name>Oprea Valentin Busu</name><email></email><affiliationId>2</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName><affiliationName affiliationId="2">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">The volume "Ioan Constantin Dima (Ed.), Systemic Approaches to Strategic Management: Examples from the Automotive Industry (pp. 396-424). Hershey, PA: IGI Global. doi:10.4018/978-1-4666-6481-4" is a high quality scientific book; it appeared at prestigious American publishing house IGI Global. The book is coordinated by Ioan Constantin Dima, Professor at "Valachia" University of Targoviste (Romania) and contains 14 chapters. Professor Dima himself contributes 7 chapters, two are developed by Professor Mariana Man (University of Petrosani, Romania), to the remaining 5 chapters contribute 10 reputed researchers: Maria Nowicka-Skowron (Czestochowa University of Technology, Poland), Janusz Grabara (Czestochowa University of Technology, Poland), Sebastian Kot (Czestochowa University of Technology, Poland), J. Novak-Marcincin (Technical University of Kosice, Slovakia), Vladimir Modrak (Technical University of Kosice, Slovakia), Ioan Cosmescu ("Lucian Blaga" University of Sibiu, Romania), Sorin Mihai Radu (University of Petrosani, Romania), Maria Macris (University of Petrosani, Romania), Dorina Tanasescu ("Valachia" University of Targoviste, Romania), Ion Stegaroiu ("Valachia" University of Targoviste, Romania). In the book are debated in a structured mode a set of major problems of strategic management as that activity that consists of decision-making involving critical organization's objectives: considerations regarding the theory of systems, system management risk, organization as system, the company on the terms of market economy, formal and informal structure of the organization, theoretical approaches of the current strategic management, theoretical approaches of company strategies, production strategies in the mining machine and machinery manufacturing industry, strategies regarding the production quality in the company. The book gathers strategies, methods, concepts, samples of high performance, tested, applied by companies in automotive industry, which is one of the most complex one. The approach represents a challenge for companies to apply the most efficiently methods, concepts regarding strategic management. New technology conjugated with strategic management applied to systems theory generate powerful companies that follow high quality of products, efficient flow production, cost reduction, environment protection, finally customer satisfaction. Thus, the book highlights the system of strategies, which the industrial companies must elaborate in order to have a favorable evolution under the current globalization conditions. By its issues, an interdisciplinary and even international approach, the book is very helpful to production specialists, scientists, students, master students, as well as to professors. </abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-126-130.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>systemic</keyword><keyword> strategic management</keyword><keyword> globalization</keyword><keyword> logistic strategies</keyword><keyword> budget</keyword></keywords></record>
<record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>131</startPage><endPage>136</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">How The Message Becomes Part Of The Communication Process</title><authors><author><name>Stefan Vladutescu</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author><author><name>Dan Valeriu Voinea</name><email></email><affiliationId>2</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName><affiliationName affiliationId="2">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">This study argues in favour of the thesis according to which the message is not directly perceived and it does not occur immediately within the communication process. We can notice that, in order to receive and understand the message, we need to follow a process concerned with the initiation into the process of comprehending the message: we receive the message after having established a hermeneutic situation and determined an instance of discourse. The message will not become obvious implicitly, within the reality of comprehension: it is not conveyed as such, as the sender does not simply deliver a message; the message takes shape within the processing of the significations used in the communicational transaction. </abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-131-136.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>message</keyword><keyword> communication</keyword><keyword> comprehension</keyword><keyword> hermeneutic situation</keyword></keywords></record>
<record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>137</startPage><endPage>142</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">The Public Broadcaster And The Dynamics Of The Romanian Radio Market</title><authors><author><name>Davian Vlad</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">University of Craiova, Romania</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">The permanent changing of the listening habits of the population and the rapid technological evolution represent a real challenge for the Romanian public radio. That is the reason why the editorial management of the public broadcaster should find the proper strategy to keep up with the transformations constantly taking place in the domestic radio market. Adapting to the New Media paradigm is a vital matter to any radio station, including the public one. Therefor the modern ways of reaching more audience should be a priority for the management of the public broadcaster, especially when the dynamics of the radio market are often spectacular and rather unpredictable. That is why the editorial strategy of the public radio must focus on the constant improvement of both the editorial offer and the means of transmission. The "battle" for rating and market share can be won only by constant adjusting and readjusting the policy of the radio station and by permanently improving the structure and the content of the radio programs. </abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-137-142.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>radio market</keyword><keyword> romanian radio</keyword><keyword> public radio</keyword><keyword> public broadcaster</keyword></keywords></record>
<record><language>eng</language><publisher>Editura Sitech</publisher><journalTitle>Social Sciences and Education Research Review</journalTitle><issn>2392-9863</issn><publicationDate>2016-12-01</publicationDate><volume>3</volume><issue>2</issue><startPage>143</startPage><endPage>149</endPage><doi></doi><publisherRecordId></publisherRecordId><documentType>article</documentType><title language="eng">A Review Of The History Of Gender Equality In The United States Of America</title><authors><author><name>Wedad Andrada Quffa</name><email></email><affiliationId>1</affiliationId></author></authors><affiliationsList><affiliationName affiliationId="1">University of Bucharest, Romania</affiliationName></affiliationsList><abstract language="eng">Gender inequality is one of the important challenges in all modern societies, the United States of America being no exception, despite the progress and significant advances that have been made in the past century. There still is a significant gender gap in many areas - most notable being the pay gap, social norms and practices, education, political participation and social institutions. The present article aims to analyse the legal framework and social framework that has evolved in the United States of America in order to diminish or completely abolish gender inequality and discrimination. After the 1920 ratification of the Nineteenth Amendment to the Constitution of the United States of America, which empowered women with political rights, there was a proposed amendment to the Constitution to guarantee equal rights for women, first introduced in Congress in 1923, passed by both houses in 1972, but which failed ratification - only 35 out of the 38 states needed ratified the amendment before the deadline - 1979, which later was extended to 1982. The United States has since taken some steps in reducing the gender gap and stopping gender discrimination: in 1963 it passed the Equal Pay Act, that prohibited pay discrimination based on sex, the next year the Civil Rights Act, which outlawed discrimination, including when based on sex, and Title IX of the Educational Amendments in 1972, which provided equal federal financial assistance indiscriminate of sex.  This legislation helped shape the United States into one of the frontrunners in gender equality, even if in 2014 it ranked on the 20th place according to the Global Gender Gap Index.</abstract><fullTextUrl format="html">http://sserr.ro/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/3-2-143-149.pdf</fullTextUrl><keywords language="eng"><keyword>equality</keyword><keyword> gender equality</keyword><keyword> gender legislation</keyword><keyword> equal rights amendment </keyword></keywords></record>
</records>